Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying roads drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
And thus a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting,
hey, there will not feel it alive,
look out below, wake up sunshine,
here we go.
Raise your flag up high,
hail a brand new dawn.
Blaze across the sky, time
to journey on, on your mark.
Come aboard with me.
We're on Earth, a legendary!.
If you can show your breath?
Then we'll make some waves!.
We run our daunted.
Ain't no beginners!.
Cause if you're wanted?
Then you're a winner!.
For we are on the cruise!.
And freedom is the only rule!.
Fearless night and day!.
Cause that's just our way!.
Find one piece!.
I'll be the first!.
I've heard it be so bad just at first?.
It's all this real!.
It must be cause my hand's on a wheel!.
I'm done playing, feel it's waiting!.
In a world I'm feeling alive!.
But I'll be loud!.
Wake up sunshine, here we go!.
We have come so far!.
Gotta make it to the end!.
Whatever danger we find,
no one ever left behind!.
I've always got your back, my friend!.
Sail on shoreward, keep marching forward!.
Dreaming from the very first
day, I'd make my name!.
And don't you know that
dream hasn't changed?.
I'm done playing through with the wave!.
In the world I'm feeling
alive, look out below!.
Wake up, sunshine!.
Wake up sunshine here!.
We go!.
We go!
Are those giant flying fish?
Darkness, too far away to
tell Is something wrong?
I can't see from in here
Mom, what are those weird fish?
Whoa, look at that!
That's not normal.
Ryugu Palace!
Ryugu Palace! Come in!
This is Border Control.
Come in.
Can anyone hear me?
Hello? Hello?
I wonder what's wrong.
I'm still not getting anything at all.
You think the snail's sick?
There's no immediate call for alarm,
but it does seem like there are a lot of
people coming in from the Fishman District.
It worries me.
That many wouldn't come at
one time just for shopping.
They're dangerous people.
Anything could happen.
Today is the day.
History will be made.
All of Fishman Island will
be united under one flag.
Mermaids, mermen, and fishmen
must all come together.
We must all be of the same mind.
We've tolerated humans long enough.
Land dwellers are inferior.
We will rule them, or they will die.
We will erase the mistakes of the
past and forge an everlasting legacy.
Ah, ho, ho, ho.
Today is the anniversary of our
engagement, dear Shirahoshi.
But it's no rush.
We don't have to get married today.
I'll wait until tomorrow.
Seems the Sun Pirates and Jinbei
have decided not to join us.
Annoying, but it isn't exactly unexpected.
We take down Neptune.
We take down Fukaboshi, Ryuboshi,
Momboshi, then we're done. Mu-hi!
Then his army-hi will fall,
assuming they don't surrender first.
Mu-hi-hi!
Yeah, but that's no fun.
I want to feast on their first.
You tell me what to cut,
and then I'll cut it.
You know the plan, right?
We split up, conquer
one area, and move on.
They won't know what hit them.
Before this day is done, the Ryugu
kingdom will fall, and we will reign!
If anyone can move, try to stop her.
It seems my theory was correct.
There's a poneglyph hidden here somewhere.
The crew can take care of themselves.
I can't miss a chance to uncover
the world's lost history.
So what if I enjoyed it?
I fought him because I had to.
I see.
Then you are a bloodthirsty butcher.
You'll turn your blade
on us next, won't you?
Look, these guys were after our
heads and probably yours too.
Did you expect us to serve them tea?
Good idea.
That sounds like a lovely
way to settle things.
Oh yeah, I'm sure they would go for that.
Who can say?
Certainly not them right now,
since you knocked them out before
we could learn why they were here.
Except it doesn't matter what they wanted
because we stopped them from doing it.
Man, I hate this.
How do we turn into the bad guys?
It's because everyone on our
crew is so irresponsible.
Or just plain violent.
Well, just look at our
captain. Good point.
Too late for regrets now.
Speaking of Luffy, I wonder if he
came across the mermaid princess.
I'd still quite like to meet her.
My poor little girl you things
what have you done to her?
Why stop crying?
I know we tied up your guards but we
didn't lay a finger on your daughter!
Liar!
Straw Hat!
Luffy took her away!
My sweet princess!
I can assure you that's not the case!
I only saw Luffy and Mr.
Shark leave the room!
Surely I would have noticed if they
had a mermaid princess with them!
If you knew her you would understand!
She would never sneak out on her own!
Also someone would notice if she
simply squam out of the room!
She takes after me when it comes to size!
Your daughter's as big as you!
Oh!
Thank you!
Why did I realize it sooner?
Straw Hat!
Hid ShiraHoshi inside Megalo's mouth!
and they all left the palace together.
Come on, your highness.
You shouldn't joke at a time like this.
That's crazy.
I know Straw Hat has a wild reputation,
but that's pretty far
out there, even for him.
That's enough.
Luffy may be a pirate,
but he's not a kidnapper.
There has to be another culprit out there.
You can't talk your way out of this one.
If my little girl doesn't come back
safe, then I'm keeping your ship!
And I'll be keeping your
friends in jail. No fear!
We're victims here, too!
I...
I did it!
Looks like they finished their job.
Not bad for a bunch of humans.
Whoa!
Hey, Sonny, looking good.
Things got pretty wild back there,
but you can't keep a super ship down.
As you can see, others weren't so lucky.
The tide brings many sunken
vessels to this spot.
It's almost like a graveyard for ships
that couldn't reach the new world.
And yet, this is a place
overflowing with life.
Thanks to the grace of the Sun Tree Eve,
many colorful fish and
coral make their home here.
And whales, too, huh?
I don't think I've ever seen
so many in one place before.
Some of them are even
bigger than the sunny.
Even if they're tucked
away in deep waters,
whales always know where fertile seas lie.
This place is a real wonderland.
It's endlessly fascinating.
No matter how much I observe,
there's always something new to find.
So it's not just me.
Even the people who live down here
think this place is a miracle.
All of Fishman Island, I mean.
I don't know how you got
wood from the Tree of Atom,
but this is a fine ship, worthy
of its parts. Damn straight.
This is my masterpiece.
Tom made a ship out of the
same stuff for Gold Roger,
so nothing less will do for my captain.
I'll do the ship coding for
you, and I'll do it with gusto.
Haven't heard that one in a while.
Oh, uh, sorry.
I never caught your name.
Call me Den.
So, Den,
don't take this the wrong way,
but for being his brother,
you sure don't look much like Tom.
I mean, you're a merman,
and he was a fish man.
Was one of you adopted or something?
That's a human-centric way to think.
I can't hardly blame you,
since family members tend to look
so much alike on the surface.
It works a bit differently with us.
We carry genes from our ancestors
that can show up in different ways,
and this rule applies to
both merfolk and fishmen.
So, if an octopus mermaid gives birth
to a shark merman, that's normal.
It just means that she, or the father, has
shark mermans somewhere in their lineage.
The bottom line is,
nothing really surprises us, no
matter what way our children turn out.
That's why it doesn't make
much sense to us when humans
discriminate against someone just
because they look a certain way.
See, the way you look doesn't
say a thing about who you are.
Speaking of which?
Was one of your ancestors?
a robot, perhaps?
That's not how it works, bro.
My mistake.
You're human, so one of
your parents was a robot?
How does that make sense?
You tell me.
It was a rhetorical question.
I should have said, I got a
letter from Granny Kokoro.
So I heard all about you and iceberg
you and the old bag stay in touch.
That's nice
Now that is one face.
I never thought I'd miss at any rate.
I heard the whole story
the good and the bad I
Know that my brother
died the very same way.
He lived with gusto
Well,
either way I do appreciate you coming here
to tell me it seems he chose his students.
Well
Oh, you're flattering me.
Are you sure you're not a robot?
Uh, well, it's complicated.
Let's drop it, okay?
By the way, I've been meaning to ask you,
there's a dude sitting
all alone over there.
Do you know who he is?
Uh-huh.
That would be the boss, Jinbei. Huh?
Boss of what?
Consider it a term of endearment.
He's waiting for someone,
but he doesn't want to enter the
island because he's a wanted man.
Intruder alert.
But the front gate.
How did you scoundrels get in here?
Well, isn't this convenient.
I was ready for a fight
but everyone's tied up.
I didn't expect much from
those pirates we sent.
Don't tell me they're
the ones who did this.
It doesn't matter.
If someone leaves you a present,
you don't ask questions.
They look scared.
I know you.
What's he doing here?
We fought so hard to keep Vandernak in
the way, and now he wants us right in.
And is that who I think it is?
Heart Jones from the Fishman District?
What does he want?
This can't be good.
Heart.
I know that man.
He once served us.
That is, he was a decorated
soldier in the Royal Army.
Actually, I'm set in thought.
Are you setting a trap for us?
Had an awful lot of visitors today, huh?
They're not like the last batch.
You did this.
You must be a cutlassist.
Just admit it.
You let them into the palace.
Really?
It's our fault?
You realize we wouldn't
even be here in the
first place if your
king hadn't invited us.
I don't know those guys.
I don't want to. They're scary.
Hey, you gotta give our weapons back.
This is bad.
We're gonna need to fight them.
Thunder Decken.
So you're the one behind this?
Straw Hat was innocent.
Give me back my daughter.
You've made her suffer enough.
All father-in-laws say that,
but you'll come around by the
time our honeymoon is over.
This I suspect I'll never
be your father-in-law.
Now where did you take Shirahoshi?
If you hung one hair on her head,
you're losing your mind, old man.
If I already had her, why would
I bother breaking in here?
Don't play dumb with me.
You're here and my daughter is missing.
The situation is clear.
Someone took my Shirahoshi.
This is a tragedy.
She's not yours and damn
right it's a tragedy.
Calm down, your highness.
This is going nowhere and
we need answers quickly.
Enough screaming.
It's a bluff.
See this?
All the pirates you threw at
her are here in the palace.
That means she must be close.
Even if Neptune is telling the truth and
she's gone, she couldn't have gotten far.
Somebody help me, miss. Eyes.
One little toss and you can
track her down anywhere.
Don't?
Tell me love has made you so blind that
you forgot how to use your own power.
His power? What's that?
Good idea. You know, Hardy,
for a muscle head, you're really
pretty clever when it comes down to it.
Well, now he's leaving?
I have a real bad feeling about this.
All right, Mr.
Coral Find my princess for me?
It is flying away.
We've been in love for ten years.
Nothing can tear us apart, princess!
Except death, that is.
And then, I had a real big fart!
That is funny, but it's
a bit inappropriate, too.
Oh, oops!
If I can't have you, then nobody can.
You're about to be a
big, beautiful corpse!
Sarah Hachi!
Flander Deccan is going to
capture my precious Karoo horse.
Oh, Neptune.
Please, I beg of you people.
I'll give you anything you ask for.
Just let me go after Deccan.
You can earn my kingdom's fortune.
You can even take my
soldiers' lives if you want.
No, King! They can't!
I can't let that beast catch Hirohoshi!
My sweetie is the not-so-little girl!
You're quite the pathetic sight, Neptune.
But what a shock.
I was confident that I
could take the palace.
But I never thought the loathsome
Straw Hats would be part of the story.
He knows us?
He's got the mark of Arlong on his arm.
Jinbei!
He tried to warn me
that there was something
wicked going on in the Fishman District.
But you, how could a former soldier
of Neptune's army be the ringleader?
Shame on you, Heart!
Shame, huh?
I'm sorry.
I can't drum up any shame.
Maybe because I never felt
pride in the army to begin with.
Listen,
there's only one reason why I joined,
and that was to learn combat skills so
I could turn this world upside down.
Simple as that. You traitor.
You helped me set things right.
What do you mean?
The comforts of your
royal palace have blinded
you to what's been
happening on this island.
Ever since I was a child, as
far back as I can remember,
I've seen fishmen oppressed
by barbaric humans.
All right, I've heard enough of your crap.
Pathetic creatures can't
even breathe underwater.
And yet, no matter how many
we kill, they don't stop.
Arlong had a fierce determination to
suffocate the arrogance out of humankind.
I deeply admired him for that.
And now, we will restore his dream.
The new Fishman Pirates
continue his legacy!
He was the reason I
cultivated my strength.
I had to train until I was strong enough
to become Arlong's right-hand man.
I dreamed of standing by his side when he
conquered the world from the East Blue.
Well, I did, until you humans came along
and crushed everything he worked for.
Oh man, I thought we
were done with Arlong.
Can't you just let it go?
What?
Not Arlong?
I'm just kidding.
In truth, I don't even know who Arlong is,
I just didn't want to
be left out, you know?
Ow! How rude!
I'll have you know that I bruise easily!
Enough chit-chat, we have
business, so let's get down to it.
Stand back!
What the...
Shark grip.
He's doing that with just his fingers?
Is he trying to break the palace down?
Okay, I am so not into this.
I'll check you later.
Kuma, I need a favor from you.
Is that his own strength? Yeah.
He hasn't taken a single energy
steroid, not yet, at least.
He just destroyed that pillar!
Damn, the creep's flooding the joint.
I came you for a banquet, not a drowning!
Oh, crap, water drops! Hit the deck!
He's gonna do it!
Shark arrows!
Who's it gonna hit the guards?
You monster!
My guards are innocent men!
How dare you shoot them down!
Leave them be!
You deranged cretin!
King Neptune!
You can't do that, sir!
Your lives are my responsibility! Ability!
Joy to snow!
Cinnabental fool!
Risking his luck for lowly pawns!
Just poor proof that you don't
have what it takes to be king!
Kidnap tools!
Damn you, Heart! Why?
They're chained and unarmed!
Damn, he's brutal!
Also, he's way stronger
than Arlong ever was!
One sword style bird dancing!
Wait, boss, please!
Can't you just move out of the way?
That creep!
He used his own Gourmet as a shield!
Hey, you two, go untie
all of the soldiers. Huh?
Our negotiation with the kingdom
it collapsed we gave them our word
to give back all the hostages
unharmed we couldn't keep that promise
that's so honest you're right i'm
on it My foot's in the water i can
feel my life draining away help me
nami wait where's nami look Huh?
She's gone?
It's not just her.
Hammy has gone missing, too.
Great.
We're losing our friends left and right.
First priority is releasing
these guys, though.
Just try to hang in there
and keep at it, brook.
Always riding my bones.
I recommend running now.
Oh, I need you to untie
your other comrades, please.
I'm afraid I don't have the energy for it.
Untie the others quickly
and take up your arms.
Don't let them do a damn thing.
Destroy the two Tommy and the Straw Hats.
Kill them all.
Special attack, Green Star Rappel Sia.
Wow, that chapter needed a giant flower.
Such exotic flora. Breathe deep.
Damn bunch of fools.
I'm dying here. Come on, Zoro. Let's move.
Listen up.
Do me a favor and help
those two get out of here.
And what about you?
We're not going to make it out of here.
Not if that guy's chasing us.
This is a revolution.
And you're in the way.
Just stay with me, Hachi.
You're gonna be okay.
You... Ugh.
No, you need to get out of here.
Quit worrying about us.
We'll be fine.
Come on, focus on you first.
What's up with the angry mob?
Give us back the mermaids!
Yeah, we're nothing but
objects to you, humans!
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb, pirates!
The word's gotten around town.
We know you did it.
We know you kidnapped all those poor
mermaids from the beach in the south.
Where did you take them, huh?
You've got the wrong guys here.
Besides, what gives you the idea
that we're the ones behind this?
I mean, I will admit...
I love mermaids so much I want
to keep them all for myself!
Regardless, our crew didn't kidnap them.
You hear that?
He just admitted that he wants them!
Will you jerk shut up?
There's a dying man here!
I knew pirates were guilty!
Get off our island!
Hey, this bottle is almost full.
That's a waste of good booze!
Shut up, human.
Oh, hey, Sanji, jumper.
Hey, Sanji, get your nose under control.
Luffy, is that a blowfish?
You know them, Luffy, your friends?
Yeah, those guys are my crew members.
Wow, interesting crew!
Look, up there, the captain
of the Straw Hat crew?
You're right, it is.
You gave the order to kidnap
the mermaids, didn't you?
We can't let all of the
people down there see me.
Hey, shut your mouth, hurry!
I'm gonna go check
things out on the ground!
He jumped off!
Hey, Hachi, what happened?
You leave Straw Hat.
Did some jerk do this to you?
Tell me who it was.
We tried, but he won't
say for some reason.
You have to get off the island.
That's the only thing he'll say.
Hang on a second.
I heard that Straw Hat had
taken over the Ryugu Palace.
It's a ploy.
He's out to kidnap more of us mermaids.
He left his men at the palace
so he could go out marauding.
I know what he wants.
He's gonna kidnap
Princess Shirahoshi, too!
Oh, don't be ridiculous.
That's absurd, and you know it.
The princess is the size of an orca.
Plus, she's the god of the
sea's only daughter, remember?
Some lowlife might dream of kidnapping
her, but nobody could pull it off. Huh?
What's up with that blowfish?
Oh, my God.
Princess Shira-ho-shiri!
I, uh, well, um, you see,
uh, good job, you found me!
She's healed! Oh, no!
Is she...
Oh, the mermaid princess!
Hey, what's up?
Something going on behind me?
No, it's nothing!
No matter what you hear,
please don't turn around!
Huh? Why?
What's the big deal?
Don't do it!
I don't want you to die, Sanji!
Oh, jeez.
The Pirates!
They kidnapped the Princess!
That's...
that's...
Princess Shirahoshi!
They they really did it
they kidnapped the princess.
Hey what the hell why'd you get
out of the shark you big baby!
I'm never so sorry Luffy please don't get
mad at me I promise it wasn't my fault.
That monster made her cry!
He's pure evil!
Oh, how could he?
More Princess Crush!
Wait.
Did he just say, Princess? Please don't!
No, Sanji!
Fight the urge to look!
Hey, I need to know, if I
turn around to look behind me,
am I going to see the mermaid princess?
I won't lie, she's behind you, and
that's exactly why you can't turn around!
The sight of an average
mermaid almost killed you!
If you see the mermaid princess,
every last drop of blood in your body
will spray out your nose like a geyser!
And then you'll be dead!
The Mermaid Princess
they say even Boa Hancock
the most beautiful
woman in the world pales
in comparison she's the
most gorgeous mermaid
who ever lived and now she's
right behind me No, Sanji!
I'm begging you, don't turn around!
Chopper, it's true.
I could give up on my dreams and
die a coward at a ripe old age.
But I'd rather reach for
the stars and die right now!
What?!
But you always told me your
dream was to find the All-Blue!
No!
Sanji!
That's her.
I never realized how
meager my imagination is.
She's magnificent.
She is quite simply
too beautiful for the mind to comprehend.
He turned to stone.
I expected death by arterial
nasal spray but this is new.
How do I even treat this?
Wait a sec.
I wonder if his blood donors
have something to do with this.
Oh, Luffy, what did I do?
Hey, what happened, huh?
Talk to me, Hachi.
Just tell me what creeps did this to you.
What the hell are you morons doing?
we caught them we actually
did it we got destroyed of
course guys like us hunt sea
kings for a living so what are
a couple of wussy pirates
gonna do those pumps are out
of their league down here
that's what you get for messing
with sea hunters you jerks
and here i thought the army
was our only hope House you
guys are fishermen you realize
we're not fish don't you
hey i remember this low life
that's right you used to be
one of our long's goons huh
You're safe now, Princess.
We saved you.
I say we turn them over to the Ammo
Knight so they can cut their heads off.
Wait, it's not what you think.
Please, Luffy's not a bad guy.
Hey, what is that?
There's something flying at us.
Look.
Really?
You think we're dumb enough to fall
for the oldest trick in the damn book?
What the?
There really is something up there.
Oh no... Not good!
IT'S FANDER DECKIN!
I FOUND YOU PRINCESS!
Come here, sweetie!
Oh no!
Please not now!
I bet he was in cahoots
with these pirates!
He's turned on his own people!
Run, princess! We'll handle this!
Just get out of here!
It's time for an answer, Shirahoshi!
It's either yes, or death!
Ha ha ha ha!
If you truly wish to live!
Then you'll marry me!
Wait, are you serious?
You've been throwing weapons at the castle
trying to kill her for
ten whole years now,
and you actually think
she's gonna marry you?
You're really twisted, Vanderdecken!
You make me sick!
The princess has been forced to live locked
up inside a tower for a whole decade,
thanks to your sick sense of romance.
Now you propose monster! Now!
Let's hear it!
Although, I do suspect that it's a yes!
Bahahahahaha!
Bahahahahahaha!
Uhhh!
Say it!
Say yes!
Bahahahaha!
You're just not my type!
AHHHHHHHHH!
AHHHHH!
What?
That's your only reason?
You trapped!
Then who is your type, huh?
After you've let me on
for ten whole years!
If you refuse to love me,
I refuse to let you exist!
Drop dead, my darling!
Run, Princess Shirahoshi, run!
Hurry, we'll fend them off with our lives!
Don't you move, you big baby!
and don't cry.
Have you caused enough trouble?
Stop telling her what to do, you jerks.
You're one of Vander
Decken's lackeys, aren't you?
You probably want the princess to die.
Look, I can't protect you if you run away.
Okay, I'll stay. No, princess.
Leave her alone, you scumbag.
You make me sick, pirate.
Real sorry about this, guys.
It's nothing personal.
But you're in my way.
Second gear!
Poofie!
He did that with his hands tied up?
Quit sticking your butt into my business!
This is between us!
You're the one who kidnapped
her from the tower, aren't you?
Listen, you jerk!
I'm gonna make sure you never throw
anything at anyone ever again!
You better hope you can back that up,
or I'm gonna throw you
both into a shallow grave!
Let me see you cry!
You let me go now!
All right, now, Gum-Gum!
Let's go!
AHHHHHH!!!
KILL MORE!
Wait!
He just...
He just beat VanderDeckan!!!
It looks like he's still alive,
but now we can catch him.
Shark!
We were together!
Hey, Sanji! You okay?
Well,
he turned to stone a few minutes back, but
he's all smiles now, and he's conscious.
Okay, that's good to hear.
Oh, princess.
I must have died and gone to heaven.
My dream came true.
My life is complete.
Once again, I'm pretty sure your
actual dream was to find the all-blue.
Hey, hurry it up!
Sorry, but please stop yelling.
It makes it hard for me to
concentrate when you do.
My heart's racing.
I don't get it.
These people don't like
us for some reason.
We gotta hurry and get out of here.
Thanks a lot. Good job. Let's go.
Okay.
What are you doing, princess?
Why did you untie him?
That evil pirate did this.
He scared her so much
she's brainwashed now.
Sorry for all the trouble.
I'll be back home in time
for dinner, I promise.
Okay, shark. Get moving.
Get back, you peasants!
Stop them now!
Wanasubi
Oh hey, I think I know that dude!
That's the Sibon to attack the Sunny!
He works for Dickens!
Oh no, it's the Great Monk!
Oh crap!
Swat them down like the insects they are!
You got it!
Second gear!
Don't go!
HITNOOOOO!
My tooth!
He broke it!
Damn worthless giant!
Okay.
Let's get a move on.
To the sea forest! Yeah!
Hey!
Hey, boss!
That pirate girl and her mermaid friend
just escaped from the Yugu Palace!
Who gives their time?
Nami-chin, should we have left
the others behind like that?
If anyone else tried to come,
we would have been caught.
Seemed like they were in trouble, though.
Those guys are fine.
Don't worry, they always
make it out alive somehow.
Yeah.
I mean, I know they're tough and all.
But there's something scary about Heart.
Hatchan said he's strong, but more
than that, he's cruel and ruthless.
They can handle it.
They've grown stronger by leaps
and bounds these past few years.
That aside, can you tell me what this
former warlord, Jinbei, is like? Huh? Oh,
well,
it's true he's a pirate, but
he's well-trusted on the island,
and they respect him enough
that he can visit the palace,
too. Really?
That's interesting, especially since
he was a part of Arlong's crew.
And now this Heart guy is presenting
himself like the second coming of Arlong.
And Jinbei made a point to
warn Luffy not to fight him.
And now I'm pretty sure
I know why that is.
Huh?
He was trying to keep him safe, right?
Just in case,
let's keep our fingers crossed that Zoro
and the others don't push Heart too far.
No matter what, though.
I want to meet this Jinbei guy.
He's waiting for Luffy at
the sea forest now, right?
We're a part of this,
whether we like it or not.
The whole kingdom could topple,
but I don't know anything about the
history behind Heart and his pirate crew.
I bet Jinbei could help us
decide how to handle this.
Wait, do you really think so?
Kuma, I need to get to the sea forest.
Right.
Listen up, soldiers.
Sir, we swear we'll take care of Heart
and the rest of his crew immediately.
No, you won't.
I'm too weak to give
you my full assistance,
and I can't let you sacrifice
your lives like that.
We shall surrender the palace for the
time being, and meet up with Fukaboshi.
We will fight back when the time is right.
You can't mean that, sir!
We can't let the palace
fall to this evil scum!
Damn it, Zoro.
I know you're strong, but do you really
think you can beat a fish man in the water?
I'm so weak. Who's up?
You know these old bones aren't the
priority, but I fear I may soon drown.
How are you going to drown
when you don't have lungs?
Good point. Ah!
Zoro!